http://www.stetsonhat.com/pages/privacy-policy

My Bag
Free Ground Shipping on Orders of $175+
Order by 12pm EST on 12/15 to get your gifts by Christmas Eve.
Last Updated: January 6, 2020
Stetson Online Store (“we”) operates the web site located at https://stetson.com/ (the “Web Site”). The Web Site includes by definition, and this Privacy Policy apply to, the Web Site itself, and any mobile app, web pages, interactive features, other applications, widgets, blogs, social networks, social network "tabs," or other online or wireless offerings that link to this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology, manner or means. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this Web Site.
Please read this privacy policy carefully, and if you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. By visiting the web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in the privacy policy.
When do we collect information?
We may collect information about you anytime you interact with us such as when you (i) access or browse the Web Site, (ii) order products or services through the Web Site, (iii) communicate with us either by e-mail, over the telephone or in any other manner, (iv) elect to participate in any of our product promotions, and (v) request information about products and services.
What information do we collect?
Information we collect is generally of two types - personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information.
We collect certain personally identifiable information defined as “information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household”)  when you sign in to the Website, create an account for online shopping register with STETSON participate in a contest, promotion or survey; or request other services that require information, registration or subscription. We also keep a record of your product interests and purchases online and automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser (including your IP address, STETSON cookie information and the page you requested).
Non-personally identifiable information comprises information that does not by itself identify an individual. This information generally includes anonymous information about an individual’s use of the Website that includes, among other things, information concerning date and time of visit, the pages of the Website visited, path through the Website, IP address, the type of browser and operating system used.
Internet Based Online Advertising and Google Analytics
This section of our privacy policy provides details about internet-based online advertising (also called "targeted advertising", "remarketing", or "behavioral advertising"), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.
We use Google Analytics’ 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender, and interests to better understand the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.
You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.
Internet Based Online Advertising and Google Analytics
This section of our privacy policy provides details about internet-based online advertising (also called "targeted advertising", "remarketing", or "behavioral advertising"), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.
We use Google Analytics’ 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender, and interests to better understand the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.
You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our Web Site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
What do we use your information for / how do we share it?
We may use your information according to the Privacy Notice and Terms of use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices with respect to the Website. We may use aggregated data (independent of any personal identifiers) for research and commercial purposes. This information includes what areas our users visit most frequently and what services they access most often. This information helps us develop a better site that is more useful and accessible to you. We may use your personally identifiable information:
To process your payment and facilitate delivery. We may also save your information to facilitate new product orders or process returns.
To create and secure your account with us.
To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.
To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.
To send you newsletters, or to provide information on products or services to you. You can elect not to receive promotional emails from us either by "unsubscribing" to an email you receive or by contacting us as indicated below.
For the purpose of operating our business, we may transfer information between Stetson and our service providers who use that information only to conduct Stetson business. For example, they may handle Stetson’s credit card processing, shipping, data management, e-mail distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We may also share your information to administer a Web Site feature. We provide our service providers with the information they need to perform their services and work with them to protect your information.
We also reserve the right to share personal information you provide with legal authorities if it is, in our sole opinion, necessary to investigate, prevent, or otherwise take action regarding suspected fraud, situations involving threats or potential harm, or if otherwise required by law (such as by a subpoena, court order, or other legal means). In the event that we reasonably believe that you have violated any of the terms or policies governing your use of the Web Site, we reserve the right to use any information we have collected about you in connection with any efforts we make or made by any of our agents on our behalf.
We may transfer information to an affiliate or third party as part of a transfer of business assets.
The below chart summarizes our collection, use, and disclosure of your information:
Types of Information Collected
Source of the Information
Purpose for Collection
Information Disclosed for a Business or Commercial Purpose? (Yes/No)
Categories of Third Parties (Which Does Not Include Service Providers) with whom the Your Information is Shared.
Identifiers (e.g., name, e-mail, postal address, and phone number)
Information directly submitted by a consumer online or offline; information collected pursuant to a transaction; information collected through communications with our customer service department; information automatically collected online (on our Site and elsewhere on the internet).
To administer and manage the Site; to deliver our services to our customers; security and fraud prevention; to develop our businesses and services; internal business operations; to process, evaluate and respond to requests and inquiries;
to conduct marketing activities, including generating leads determining and managing the effectiveness of our own and our customers’ advertising and marketing campaigns; to monitor and enforce compliance with our terms; and/or any other purposes for which you provided the information.
Yes
Business partners, customers, third party web tracking providers, and marketing channels.
Demographic Information
Information directly submitted by a consumer online or offline; information collected pursuant to a transaction; information collected through communications with our customer service department; information automatically collected online (on our Site and elsewhere on the internet).
To administer and manage the Site; to deliver our services to our customers; security and fraud prevention; to develop our businesses and services; internal business operations; to process, evaluate and respond to requests and inquiries;
to conduct marketing activities, including generating leads determining and managing the effectiveness of our own and our customers’ advertising and marketing campaigns; to monitor and enforce compliance with our terms; and/or any other purposes for which you provided the information.
Yes
Business partners, customers, third party web tracking providers, and marketing channels.
Financial Account Information
Provided by users.
To complete a transaction requested by the consumer.
Yes
Not shared.
Commercial Information (e.g., purchase histories)
Information directly submitted by a consumer online or offline; information collected pursuant to a transaction; information collected through communications with our customer service department; information automatically collected online (on our Site and elsewhere on the internet).
To administer and manage the Site; to deliver our services to our customers; security and fraud prevention; to develop our businesses and services; internal business operations; to process, evaluate and respond to requests and inquiries;
to conduct marketing activities, including generating leads determining and managing the effectiveness of our own and our customers’ advertising and marketing campaigns; to monitor and enforce compliance with our terms; and/or any other purposes for which you provided the information.
Yes
Business partners, customers, third party web tracking providers, and marketing channels.
Website Browsing Activity
Information directly submitted by a consumer online or offline; information collected pursuant to a transaction; information collected through communications with our customer service department; information automatically collected online (on our Site and elsewhere on the internet).
To administer and manage the Site; to deliver our services to our customers; security and fraud prevention; to develop our businesses and services; internal business operations; to process, evaluate and respond to requests and inquiries;
to conduct marketing activities, including generating leads determining and managing the effectiveness of our own and our customers’ advertising and marketing campaigns; to monitor and enforce compliance with our terms; and/or any other purposes for which you provided the information.
Yes
Business partners, customers, third party web tracking providers, and marketing channels.
SELLING INFORMATION
We do not sell your personal information that is collected under this Privacy Notice. To the extent we sell any personal information that falls outside the scope of this Privacy Notice, we will disclose our selling practices in the applicable privacy notices linked below.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
To enhance your use of the Website and shopping experience , we or our service providers  use cookies (small text files stored in a user’s browser) or Web beacons (electronic images that allow us to count users who have accessed particular content and to access certain cookies) to collect aggregate data. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at here http://www.aboutcookies.org.
Some cookies we use are necessary to enable you to navigate the Website and use features such as registering or creating and logging in your account.  We also use cookies to gather and record information about choices you make on the Website and to allow us to tailor to our visitors.
The cookies we or our service providers may use on our Website include:
Necessary Cookies: These cookies are necessary for the Website to function and cannot be switched off in our system. These cookies are usually only set in response to actions made by you which include a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences or logging into your account.
Analytics Cookies: These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of the Website. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the Website.
Marketing & Retargeting Cookies:  These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.
If you prefer not to receive cookies through our Website, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only "trusted" websites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site and use it.
By using this website, you agree that we can place cookies on your computer or device as explained above. However, you can control and manage cookies in various ways. Please note that removing or blocking cookies may limit system performance and may impact your user experience and parts of the Website may no longer be fully accessible.
If you refuse cookies, this may limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction or not to work at all. You can learn more about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies.
We do not use technology that recognizes a "do-not-track" signal from your web browser.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on the Web Site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Web Site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a resident of California, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request once a calendar year information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by STETSON to a third party for the third party’s direct marketing purposes. Please note that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.  This right granted to California residents applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please fill out this form or call us at 855-655-8979.
Please direct any rights requests (as further described below) or additional questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy via email to: help@stetson.com. If you do, we will need to collect your information such as your name, email or transaction history in order to verify your identity. You may also authorize an agent to make a request on your behalf, who will need to provide similar information for verification.
Deletion. California residents have the right to request the deletion of information.
Access. You may request to receive details about how we collect, use, and share your personal data. Specifically, you may request to receive the specific pieces of personal data that we have collected about you.
Non-Discrimination. We do not discriminate against you for exercising any CCPA rights, such as the access and deletion rights described above. If we choose to offer a product enhancement or financial incentive that is contingent on you sharing personal information, we will ensure that the value provided to us by that collection is reasonably related to the value of the product enhancement or financial incentive.
California law also provides that California residents are entitled to know how this site responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. Like many other websites and online services, this site does not currently alter its practices when it receives Do Not Track signals because there is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” and for opt out information, you may wish to visit www.aboutads.info.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. As a parent or guardian you can request us to remove personal information of your child that was submitted without your consent or by misrepresenting his or her age. At your request, we will take reasonable steps to remove such information from our database. All such requests should include the same user name, password, and e-mail address that your child submitted and should be sent to help@stetson.com.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Web Site and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Web Site.
Integrity
During the account sign-in process you can review, change or remove the information you have submitted. We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible and encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes. You may, at any time, access your information to update, modify or delete any inaccuracies by accessing your account through the Web Site. You may also request us to remove your account information from our databases and we will try to remove as much information as possible. However, as we generally keep information related to past transactions for our records, we will not be able to completely remove your information.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change our policy at any time by posting a new version of it on the Web Site. We encourage you to check the Web Site regularly for information about revisions to this Privacy Policy. In the event that we change our Privacy Policy, such changes will affect all of the information we collect after any such change. If you object to the change to our Privacy Policy, then you must contact us in writing regarding your objection.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Email: help@stetson.com
Stetson Online Store
Attn: Privacy Policy 946 W. 17th Street Costa Mesa, CA 92627 USA
JOIN OUR NEWSLETTER
Subscribe to stetson.com emails to receive early access to exclusive offers & 10% off your first purchase!
Gender
Male
Female
No Thanks
By providing your email address, you agree to our Privacy Policy & Terms & Conditions.
Please enter a valid e-mail address
You have successfully joined our newsletter
